Daryl Hepting: So Can everybody hear me all right?
Come on yeses. Okay. How's everyone doing today?
So just as we're getting people into the meeting,
me,
maybe didn't hear the notice about recording.
So, in my last
attempt to record the meeting,
Unknown: my recording didn't
cut out partway through
Daryl Hepting: and I've been experimenting with it. a transcript
Unknown: Is that returned to me to
audible
so the idea of Was I was trying.
So,
here's a message to begin with. I think you can see
beside my name, there's a little card with a.on it that says it's recording. So
the idea is that we can have an audio
recording and a transcript at the meeting.
I will
keep your name
All right, so lots of things going on here. So what I want to do first of all is
to start sharing my screen
and we can look at the website
All right, so here's the updated version.
That should be on the website
soon. And
this is from ours, our chat session on
on Thursday.
So I'm experimenting
with the display so you can let me know what you think so I
so DHH that's me
In case you're wondering.
So DHH Daryl H Hepting. You can call me Daryl R. Dr. Hepting.
I'd like you to pick one of those two.
So this is the way that I presented it. So anything that was sent to me
privately,
I have not included
so what I've done is I
What am I gonna say But
so, the identifiers are consistent so every time the students student who said
hello as 1129 on Thursday rota write something they'll come in.
So
we can
keep track of people but not
by names.
This is a good thing or
or not
Thanks to Sam who points out everyone should have gotten a note that the meeting
is recorded.
So I just wanted to
let you know that
why I'm recording it so that
we had so we're not going to share. I'm not going to share the video with you
but
I'll make the
audio recording available
to be accessible through the
through the
meeting blanks
and
Then I can also get a
transcript
which I'll
so am I sharing the
zoom chat for meeting
or not
Okay, what am I sharing
Okay, on the
Okay, I'm gonna try and
share the right window this time.
look better
Okay, so now I can make sense that I can ask a question again about any thoughts
about the display of the transcript
She can see now.
Okay, so I think we have everybody in the room now
and
Yeah, okay, so the couple of comments on the chat parents script.
Okay, so let me say a few things. So the comment about recording the screen so
I'm not interested in the video recording maybe I, I'll look at it to see if
it's if it's possibly helpful.
But that's not
my reason for recording. My reason for recording is the audio and the
automatic Transcript generation.
Although the documentation says the transcript will be ready shortly after the
video is ready, but in my case, the test I did on Thursday and Friday. It was a
long time hours. So maybe we can expect to see the track transcript of our of
the audio.
Tomorrow, sometime
so when we have the transcript of the audio,
it might be helpful. It couldn't transcript on the transcript to the audio that
might help to give context to chat. So you can see when things are going on.
And so regarding
the
de identified
students
I was thinking of doing some editing on this.
But then
I thought just to let it go ahead and
be
be an accurate representation of what
happened.
For people said
three people said hello and one person said Good morning at 1130 on Thursday,
then
I would just
be fine to represent that.
So, I making the public version of this
transcript available
to help large class discussions.
But I still have the names
of people. So regarding missing the actual student names to me, that's a feature
Such a feature but I have them
okay
So in terms of the length,
so
this is possibly a
helpful feature.
We can close parts as well.
And one of the times
is it better to represent
this is not, you don't have this is something to think about. Well, I could
increase the usefulness of this in terms of
the timestamps.
So would it be helpful to have
visual representation of the passage of time.
So 1129 3031 and then have a gap
between 31 and 35
and so on and then 4445 4647 and then there was a gap until noon.
So instead of suggestion is instead of time stamps
the question prompted the responses.
So
I think that's
a worthy, worthy goal, to be able to have that
connection.
It's a little bit hard to do.
So I'm going to gonna hope that the transcript will
help that
provide that context.
So the reason I didn't include seconds
in the
in the timestamp was to group
common sense Same time.
I didn't. I thought
it might be helpful to have some grouping of them rather than
just have each each
timestamp, comment or chat message
on its own
Okay, so
thank you think about
how to use this.
And
we can talk about somar
on Thursday,
but how can we use
Okay, how can this data be
as helpful as possible?
So, if you're going to say,
what do you think of that question? Think about for next day How could you
present the chat data so that it is helpful as possible.
Is that enough information?
So something that happens happening here is there's a delay in
the chat.
Now just coming up on
the chat are
chat is an asynchronous communication form here
because you can have that one
and that's both a positive and a negative because we have to try and put things
back together in terms of a threat.
That's not unlike doing an
instant messaging
in some form or another,
say if somebody if the person you're talking to asks two different questions
before you can answer the first question.
And maybe you start to talk about the first question
before in more than one message before you get to
question two.
And so it seems to be not very hard to
to have things diverge a bit.
Yeah,
okay. So my hope is that
the
to present the transcripts of the audio, that to say
together in a similar format
with
the chat
I have a feeling
Okay, so
I'm gonna work on presenting
for Thursday my homework will be to format the audio transcript in,
in a way similar to the
to the chat transcript.
I have a suspicion though.
The timestamp in the
video is from the beginning of the recording notch. Not
not the time of day that
is being used in the chat. So, there might be an issue of synchronizing that
although you think this is not a new problem, so
I wonder if
there's some ways to
put them together.
Anyway, I'll see what I get back. We could talk about this tomorrow on
Thursday.
So is everyone able to get to access your courses now? All the 40 people in the
zoom chat or the zoom meeting, can
access your courses.
Can you do a half a checkmark
or an x? For Yes or no?
See no if I try and add the question into the stream in the chat stream
What I noticed is
so we have 20 people voting yes
if you're not able to 2122 23
Sorry, I wasn't
I asked her
show, show check mark or
exes for yes or no.
So
I'm wondering should should we,
you? Okay, so 28 out of 40 of your courses access. So if you don't have your
courses x and a send me a note or an email, I'll get you sorted out. Okay.
So I'm going to clear that.
So the question next question is
All questions.
Yes.
No
the
gained one and then we lost two.
So here's the
here's an interesting question. So I'm asking
whether we should put responses into the chat.
So when I asked her yes or no checkmarks
So last time I asked her yes or no checkmarks I got a stream stream of yeses in
the chat transcript when the chat window
but now
the people who are voting for
chat
holding it six to four
none of the people who said yes in the chat said
None of the positive responses
are in the chat window.
Okay, there's one.
I stand corrected. There's at least one positive response. And I agree with them
is a bit ambiguous even though we're just
although it seems like a no.
Okay.
Here's a question.
Who has seen the textbook?
Yes or no
Sorry I cleared the answer. So
So
I think that's my cat.
anyone remembers from anyone who was here in
March
the cute looking one
on my lap
anyway
Okay,
okay, so that was me reporting the results Okay.
Okay.
So
in the process of getting the textbook
Oh, so I didn't hit return there between my report of the results and
next class response to the question about online access, so
Here it is, and I've put in the links. I've updated the links on the webpage
there.
So
there are
slides
available for each chapter.
So
chapters one and two Fisher's thing
I'm not sure whether the website is mobile friendly.
I can't look at it right now.
You can see whether
how it appeared. Whether you have a good experience with that website on your
mobile device
I like the enthusiasm in the chat room with all the exclamation points
flying around.
Okay, so
So I'm getting some reports that the website is working on low file.
I would say that there's more to
march working.
There's more to it than just working.
So working is the is the bottom rung
on the list. So first of all,
you can you're caught so that's the question is can you accomplish a given task
with a website? And if you can answer yes.
So then he might say that it's effective.
If it's a little
bit better to
work with so that you can see
how you might do other things, then things are well organized. And then the next
step up is maybe
comprehensible so that you can
you can decide what actions come next.
And then
a step above that is whether it's satisfying.
So
So what are some ways that we can think of being satisfying
Don't have to think about what to do.
We want to do is
easily available.
What are some other ways that we can think about being satisfying? So let's
clear with what happens between
if we have a goal in mind
commands to achieve the goal are clear. And when we look at the state of the
system, we can easily and correctly interpret the state and what needs to be
done to go from the current state to our goals state. So I'm going to try and
draw something
with my iPad here. Give me a second.
Okay, let me see if I can.
That's my son handiwork. Here
we can see some UCF
All right, I'm ready to draw.
Can you see that?
Give me a yes or no.
If you can see, okay.
So I have human computer
if I write
single words maybe they're not too illegible
Okay, so clicking back to our discussion last day about
how to use those Chevron's to indicate
progressive discovery.
So I saw that that term was used in the Microsoft interface guidelines. And I've
got a few links that I'll
put up about that.
So let's, let's see issue.
So, if we point the arrow
up or down, then can indicate the
So we're either moving up or down to reveal more content than the question. So
that makes more sense. I can understand the argument that makes more sense than
having a sideways arrow and tip it down to display because of sideways because a
direction that we're going off the screen and maybe that's appropriate for when
for menus, and so on.
But not necessarily from
the idea that there's
content to be displayed within in place.
Then the question is
keep them separate so the question is
so just an aside here I've got,
I don't you can see this.
I've got to put a dialog box has come up and says, MP devices agent wants to use
your confidential information in your key chain. I just seen I've just seen an
ad from Apple about how
they're big on privacy. So
good. Good for them, too. To ask for permission, but there's no indication of
what ANP devices agent
is, and if it's
what it wants to do with, like confidential information.
So I'm gonna say, I have an idea about that. I'm gonna deny it for now. And you
can still see it, I think, looks to me like you can.
Alright, so
So now the question is to use the app
to use this to indicate
The state or the command.
So should we see it when
this content is an
extra content is displayed, indicating then that it's
commands that we can use to
to hide the content
or should we see it when
the content is closed and then that indicates the state of content hidden behind
or below the
or that can be revealed by clicking.
So the same thing here
So, Commander state that's a question that we see and we work with or we're
dealing with and when we look at the computer and then
we tried to make sense of it, we say
I wonder what this
is. So this is an example of how the process of evaluation
And then you say, Well, I want to see more content.
But till I do
so I think I'm gonna press that
inverted v up.
The Chevron is pointing up to reveal more content.
So this is my goal is to do more content I
can decide, I think that this is the way to go about it
and then I can see whether or not what I've done is helping the situation
helping me to achieve my goal.
So this is a pretty small example and
so we can't get
into too much trouble here
if you think otherwise But
so long as we have a representation. So let's see, the question is
if we have these icons
giving the feedback,
then that's the question is really not as that command or is it representing the
state?
So we can't get
too far away. But if if we have such choices which are for our less clear,
let's say how do I
display in
the chat from Monday from Thursday's meeting
related To
the question about Chevron's
and that's a little bit
more involved. And
if if we can
go to the record for meeting one and see the chat transcript and then look
through it, then that's a fairly strict and that seems like a reasonable thing
to do.
And we
we don't have up too much chance to make
mistakes. So
yeah, as we're pointing at the screen
out of habit
Call from execution
Can anyone
fill in the blank here golf
starts with any
you have a put your hand up if you want to answer
Okay, Richmond will turn your mic on
me
stretching. I think
it's catching inflammation.
That's right. The inflammation. Yes. So starting with the knee, so
it's our
dealing with evaluation.
Okay. Okay.
Thanks. Sure. Sorry, I. So if I call on you there's also a way for you to think
it's the spacebar to turn your own microphone on
thank you for the answer.
So coffer
ation.
So if we have a satisfying experience these, these scoffs are small. And if we
have a frustrating experience, the costs are large.
Make sense?
Like if you have to, if you're scratching your head and thinking about how do I
accomplish my goal and then
a very large golf
well, golf that we're dealing with
Okay, so it's
two minutes left. Any questions or concerns that you want to
express?
So a question or Discord. Yeah, I just I'm going to figure that out. And I'll
send an invitation. I'll put an invitation on your courses.
Chris Harris
So for office hours, I was thinking,
I have a meeting at 3pm today so
and it sir, it's quarter to one here. So about 130 to 230 today.
And then
11 to noon tomorrow
and
130 to 230 on Thursday.
And if you have questions outside of that you can
send me and you know how to get ahold of me.
You can use the URL courses or send me email to Derek there Hepting at URI
gianna.ca. And I have a link on your courses page. Okay, so I'll post my
artist's rendering of the concept of gulf of execution evaluation.
And we'll
so have a have a look at the
first two chapters of material from the textbook beyond interaction, primary
interaction design. And I didn't we didn't talk about my in plate, robot attack
video, all 13 seconds of it. So if you can have a look at that, and we'll talk
about that too, on Thursday. Okay, thanks very much for your time.
See you on Thursday.